Guide to the Karen Landahl Papers 1940-2004
University of Chicago Library
- Series V: Writing by Others
  - Flege, J. and H. Hillenbrand – Limits on Phonetic Accuracy in Foreign Language Speech Production - Journal of the Acoustic Society of America, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Fowler, Rubin, Remez, and Turvey – Implications for Speech Production of a General Theory of Action, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Fowler, C. – An Event Approach to the Study of Speech Perception from a Direct-Realist Perspective – Journal of Phonetics, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Fowler, Best, and McRoberts – Young Infants' Perception of Liquid Coarticulatory Influences on Following Stop Consonants – Perception and Psychophysics, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Frege, Gottlob - On sense and Reference (1892) - The Logic of Grammar, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Fujimara, O. – Methods and Goals of Speech Production Research – Language and Speech, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Fujimara, O., and J. Lovins – Syllables as Concatenative Phonetic Units - Syllables and Segments, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Gay, T. – Temporal and Spatial Properties of Articulatory Movements - The Cognitive Representation of Speech, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Georgian, Logemann, and Fisher – Compensatory Articulation Patterns of a Surgically Treated Oral Cancer Patient - Journal of Speech and Hearing Disorders, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Gilbert, J. – Acoustical Features of Children's Vowel Sounds, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Goldstein, M. – Speech without a Tongue - The Journal of Speech Disorders, March 1940 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Grice, H.P. – Logic and Conversation – The Logic of Grammar, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Han and Weitzman - Acoustic Features of Korean /P, T, K/, /p, t, k/ and /ph, th, kh/1 - Phonetica, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Hardcastle, W.J. – Some Observations on the Tense-Lax Distinciton in Initial Stops in Korean - Journal of Phonetics (fragment), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Hillin, W.A., M. Fry and R. Hershman – Computer Recognition of Spoken Digits Based on Six Nonacoustic Measures – Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Hirose, Lee, and Ushijima - Laryngeal Control in Korean Stop Production - Journal of Phonetics (fragment), 1974 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - House and Fairbanks – The Influence of Consonant Environment Upon the Secondary Acoustical Characteristics of Vowels - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1952 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Institute for Academic Technology - "Technology in Higher Education" series - Multiple articles, 1989-1990 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Isshiki, N. and R. Ringel – Air Flow during the Production of Selected Consonants – Journal of Speech and Hearing Research, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Jakobson, Fant, Halle – Preliminaries to Speech Analysis: The Distinctive Features and their Correlates, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, K. – Multiple papers, 1998 and undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Karnell, Michael P. - Curriculum vitae and multiple articles, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Kazazis, K. – Dismantling Greek Diglossia (fragment), undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Kewley-Port, D. and D.B. Pisoni – Identification and Discrimination of Rise Time: Is it Categorical or Noncategorical? – Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, April 1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Kewley-Port, D. - Time-Varying Features as Correlates of Place of Articulation in Stop Consonants – Journal of the Acoustic Society of America, January 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Klein, Martin J. - The Physics of J. Willard Gibbs in His Time - Physics Today, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Kurowski, K. and S.E. Blumstein – Perceptual Integration of the Murmur and Formant Transitions for Place of Articulation in Nasal Consonants - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, August 1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Ladefoged, P. and D.E. Broadbent – Information Conveyed by Vowels - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Lehiste, I., and D. Meltzer – Vowel and Speaker Identification in Natural and Synthetic Speech, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Levitt, A. et al – Context Effects in Two-Month-Old Infants' Perception of Labiodental/Interdental Fricative Contrasts - Journal of Experimental Psychology, Human Perception and Performance, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lieberman, P. – On the Development of Vowel Production in Young Children – Child Phonology, Volume I: Production, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Lieberman, A. and Mattingly - The Motor Theory of Speech Perception Revised – Cognition, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Lieberman, Cooper, Shankweller, and Kennedy – Perception of the Speech Code - Psychological Review, 1967 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Lindblom, B. – Spectographic Study of Vowel Reduction - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Local, J. – Syllabification and Rhythm in Non-Segmental Phonology, undated (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Lotto, Kluender, and Holt - Animal Models of Speech Perception Phenomena, Chicago Linguistic Society, 1997; and Perceptual Compensation for Coarticulation by Japanese Quail, Journal of the Acoustic Society of America, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Lumsden, C.J. – Neuronal Group Selection and the Evolution of Hominid Cranial Capacity – Journal of Human Evolution, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - MacWhinney, B. – Hungarian Language Acquisition as an Exemplificaiton of a General model of Grammatical Development, undated (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - MacWhinney, B. – Competition and Cooperation in Language Processing, undated (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Maddieson, I. – Phonetic Cues to Syllabification, undated (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Maddieson, I. and K. Precoda – Syllable Structure and Phonetic Models, undated (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Malmberg, B. – The Phonetic Basis for Syllable Division, undated (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Makashay, M.J and K. Johnson – Surveying Auditory Space Using Vowel Formant Data, undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Mann, Virginia – Influence of Preceding Liquid on Stop Consonant Perception – Perception and Psychophysics, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Mann, Virginia – Distinguishing Universal and Language-Dependent Levels of Speech Perception: Evidence form Japanese Listners' Perception of English "I" and "r" - Cognition, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Massaro, D. and W. Idsom – The Role of Perceived Duration in the Identification of Vowels - Journal of Phonetics, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Miller, James D. – Auditory Processing of the Acoustic Patterns of Speech –Arch Otolaryngol, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Miller and Eimas - Studies on the Categorization of Speech by Infants - Cognition, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Miller, R.L. – Nature of the Vocal Cord Wave - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Mochizuki-Sudo, M. and S. Kiritani – Production and Perception of Stress-Related Durational Patterns in Japanese Learners of English, - Journal of Phonetics, 1991 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Ohala, John J. – Multiple articles, 1974-1990 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Ohman, Sven E. G. – Numerical Model of Coarticulation – Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Oller, D.K. and B.L. Smith – Effect of Final-Syllable Position on Vowel Duration in Infant Babbling – Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Palmer, J.M. – Dynamic Palatography - Phonetica, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Parker, E. and R. Diehl – Identifying Vowels in CVC Syllables: Effects of Inserting Silence and Noise - Perception and Psychophysics, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Pike – Phonetic Symbolism, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pos, van der Kamp, and Plomp - Perceptual and Physical Space of Vowel Sounds - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Rakerd, B. – Vowels in Consonantal Context are Perceived More Linguistically than are Isolated Vowels: Evidence from an Individual Differences Scaling Study – Perception & Psychophysics, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Rentschler and Mann – The Effects of Glossectomy on Intelligibility of Speech and Oral Perceptual Discrimination - Journal of Oral Surgery, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Repp, B. – Phonetic Trading Relations and Context Effects: New Experimental Evidence for a Speech Mode of Perception - Psychological Bulletin, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Rosenberg, A.E. – Effect of Glottal Pulse Shape on the Quality of Natural Vowels – The Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Rothenberg, M. – A New Inverse-Filtering Technique for Deriving the Glottal Air Flow Waveform during Voicing – Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Schouten and Pols – Vowel Segments in Consonantal Contexts: A Spectral Study of Coarticulation - Part I - Journal of Phonetics, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Skelly, Donaldson, Fust, and Townsend - Changes in Phonatory Aspects of Glossectomee Intelligibility Through Vocal Parameter Maniuplation - Journal of Speech and Hearing Disorders, undated (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Smith, Allen, Warren, and Hall - The Consistency of the Pressure-Flow Technique for Assessing Oral Port Size - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Smith, R. – Edwin P. Hubble and the Transformation of Cosmology - Physics Today, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Soli, S.D. – The Role of Spectral Cues in Discrimination of Voice Onset Time Differences – Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Sondhi, M. – "Model for Wave Propagation in a Lossy Vocal Tract," and "Measurement of the Glottal Waveform" - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1974 and 1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Stark, J., Lindblom, B. and Sundberg, J. – APEX an Articulatory Synthesis Model for Experimental and Computational Studies of Speech Production - Current Research in Speech Physiology, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Stathopoulos, E.T. – Oral Air Flow during Vowel Production of Children and Adults - Cleft Palate Journal, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Stevens, Kenneth N., et al. - "Perturbation of Vowel Articulations by Consonantal Context: An Acoustical Study," and "Invariant Cues for Place of Articulation in Stop Consonants," 1963 and 1978 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Straight, H.S. – Auditory versus. Articulatory Phonological Processes and Their Development in Children - Child Phonology, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Subtelny and Worth - Intraoral Pressure and Rate of Flow during Speech - Journal of Hearing and Speech Research, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Suomi, K. – On Spectral Coarticulation in Stop-Vowel Syllables: Implications for Automatic Speech Recognition – Journal of Phonetics, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Terrace, Pettito, Sanders, and Bever – Can an Ape Create a Sentence? - Science, 1979 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Trullinger, R.W., and F.W. Emanuel – Airflow Characteristics of Stop-Plosive Consonant Productions of Normal-Speaking Children – Journal of Speech and Hearing Research, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - van Hattum and Worth – Air Flow Rates in Normal Speakers, undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Wakita, H. – Instrumentation for the Study of Speech Acoustics, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Walley and Carrell – Onset Spectra and Formant Transitions in the Adult's and Child's Perception of Place of Articulation in Stop Consonants - Journal of Acoustical Society of America, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Warren, Donald W. – Multiple articles, 1964, 1981, and undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Weintraub, Mesulam, and Kramer – Disturbances in Prosody: A Right-Hemisphere Contribution to Language - Archives of Neurology, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Werker and Tees – Developmental Changes across Childhood in the Perception of Non-native Speech Sounds – Canadian Journal of Psychology, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - White, J.P. – Acoustic and Perceptual Characteristics of Electronic Artificial Larynges - Dissertation, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Winters, S., and K. Johnson – An Exemplar-Based Model of Silent-Center Syllable Perception, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Zwicker, Flottorp, and Stevens – Critical Band Width in Loudness Summation - Journal of the Acoustical Society of America, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Series VI: Professional Activities
  - Conference presentations – Papers, overhead projector transparencies, and slides 1979-1987 and undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Conference presentations - Papers 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Conference presentations - Abstracts, papers, and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Origin of Human Language, Cortona, Italy – Programs and Group Photograph, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Chicago Linguistic Society 33 – Schedules, presentation, and overhead projector transparencies, April, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Series VII: Teaching
  - Experimental Phonetics – Readings, 1961-1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Notes – Child Phonology, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Linguistics 304 – Syntax I – Student Assignments, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Linguistics 304 – Syntax I – Readings and student papers, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Student lab results, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Linguistics 301 – Introduction to Linguistics – Student Papers, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Student labs, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Student term papers, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Student Assignments and Labs, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Student Labs, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Student Labs, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Quizzes, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Quizzes and Instructions, 1988-1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Photograph - Karl-Eric, May 1988 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Introduction to Language Development - Readings evaluations, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Anne Farley - Phonological Acquisition Exam and Dissertation Proposal, "The Role of Imitation in Language Acquisition," 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Linguistics 306 - Phonetics – Notes and Quizzes, Student Lists, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Linguistics 306 - Phonetics – Labs, Course Plans, Readings, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Linguistics 306 - Phonetics – Labs, Quizzes and Assignments, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Eunlim Kim - Study and dissertation proposals, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Bob Mitchell - M.A. Paper Proposal, Progress Reports, and 7-inch reel-to-reel audiotape, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Linguistics 200/300 - Talking Computers and Visible Speech for Language Study - Syllabi and readings, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Linguistics 200/300 - Talking Computers and Visible Speech for Language Study - Readings, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Linguistics 200/300 - Talking Computers and Visible Speech for Language Study - Readings, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Caroline Wiltshire - Phonetics Minor Exam Reading List, January 1991 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Kenneth Cordes - M.A. Thesis, "Interactions between Consonants and Tones in Taiwanese Hokkien," 1991 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Convocation program, June 14, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Linguistics 469, Phonetics/Phonology Interface - Draft syllabus (1996) and photocopied articles, 1981-1996 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Applied Phonetics Instruction Manual, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Linguistics 206/306, Phonetics - Syllabus, lab manual, lab assignments, photocopied articles, and phonetics wheel, 1992-1997 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Lab Manual, Lab Assignments, and Quizzes, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Linguistics 306 – Phonetics – Lab Demonstration, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Phonetics – Group Lab Work and student notecards, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Phonetics, Major Field Exam - Reading lists, reading abstracts, and photocopied articles, 1993-1998 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Taping instructions - undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Early speech research bibliography - Photocopied articles, 1952-1985 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Early speech research bibliography - Photocopied articles, 1970-1980 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Early Work on Vowel Perception and Motor Theory bibliography - Photocopied articles, 1946-1985 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Imitation bibliography - Photocopied articles, mainly just page 1, 1961-1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Imitation bibliography - Photocopied index cards and articles, and offprints, 1971-1985 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Imitation bibliography - Photocopied articles, 1957-1984 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Imitation bibliography - Photocopied articles, 1957-1984 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Imitation bibliography - Photocopied articles, 1957-1984 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Imitation bibliography - Photocopied articles, 1969-1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Photocopied articles and offprints, 1946-2004 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1960-1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1967-1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Photocopied articles and offprints, 1974-1982 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1981-1997 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1976-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1973-1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1979-1983 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1967-1982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Photocopied articles and chapters, 1987-1992 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Photocopied articles and conference papers, 1986-1995 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Series VIII: Oversize
  - Vowel Data Graphs, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Vowel Data Graphs and Spectograms, circa 1977 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Series IX: Restricted
  This series contains restricted personnel and financial information, grant proposals with social security numbers, evaluative student material, and medical information. Materials in Box 38 are restricted for 50 years from date of record creation. Materials in Box 39 are restricted for 80 years from date of record creation. Materials in Boxes 40-50 are restricted indefinitely.
  - Personnel Records, UIC Medical Center, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Modeling of Abnormal Vocal Tracts - Grant proposal, circa 1982 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Imitation in Phonological Acquisition - Study proposals, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Travel reimbursement forms, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Language Lab - GW Instruments purchase orders, invoices, and warranties, 1986-1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Japanese Visi-Pitch - Financial reports, 1989-1990 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - ESPS/Waves+ - Purchase packet, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Workshop budgets, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - The Structure of Sound as an Information Channel - National Science Foundation proposal, correspondence, and CVs, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Grant application, circa 1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Hearing and Perception in Cleft Palate Infants - Grant application, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Speech Production Studies in Craniofacial Anomalies - Grant application, correspondence, notes, progress reports, and photocopied articles, 1983-1985 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Replacement of acoustic spectrum analyzer - Grant application, Campus Research Board, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Otitis Media, Sensory Deprivation and Speech Sound Perception - Grant applications, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Speech Production in Craniofacial Anomalies - Grant application, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Speech Production in Craniofacial Anomalies - Grant application, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Masters Thesis - Angela Hasner, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Introduction to Linguistics - Graded student work, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Student papers, labs, and grades, 1988-1990 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Dissertation proposal - Anne Farley, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Dissertation introduction - Eunlim Kim, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Ectrodactyly-Ectodermal Dysplasia - Clefting (ECC) - Case notes, 1958-1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Spectograms - F-, 1968-1974 and undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Spectograms - F- 2 months, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Apert patient data and spectrograms, 1972-1976 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Apert patient data and spectrograms, 1972-1977 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Spectograms, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Patient data - Crouzon #3493, Crouzon #3589, and Apert #1949, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #1909, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #1949, 1972 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #1949, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #1949, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #1013, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #984, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #984, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #2183, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #2183, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Apert #2023, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Apert patient images, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Crouzon #3493, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Crouzon #3493, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Crouzon #3589, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Crouzon #3589, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Crouzon #3589, 1977-1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Crouzon #2033, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Patient data and spectrograms - Crouzon #2033, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Forms and notes, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Directory and patient data, 1976-1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Patient data, correspondence, and signed permission forms for audio recording of underage children, 1983-1986 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Parents' or Guardians' permission for audio recording of underage child - Signed forms, 1983-1986 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Cleft Palate Clinic - Patient data, 1984-1986 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Tape transcripts - D-, 1975-1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Tape transcripts - D-, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Tape transcripts - D-, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Tape transcripts - J-, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Tape transcripts - M-, 1979-1980 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Tape transcripts - M-, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Tape transcripts - S-, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Tape transcripts - S-, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Tape transcripts - S-, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Tape transcripts - S-, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Tape transcripts - S-, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Patient addresses, taping instructions, and correspondence, circa 1983-1987 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Tape transcripts - A-, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Tape transcripts and notes - C-, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Center for Craniofacial Anomalies - Patient data - E-, 1984-1985 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Tape transcripts - E-, 1984-1985 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Spectograms - G-, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Patient notes and tape transcripts - K-, 1983-1985 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Patient notes and tape transcripts - K-, 1983-1986 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Patient notes - K-, 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Patient notes and tape transcripts - K-, 1985-1986 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - I.E.P. and correspondence - U-, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 7)